{
    "subject": "resource/Thiruvisaippa",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Thiruvisaipa (Tamil: \u0ba4\u0bbf\u0bb0\u0bc1\u0bb5\u0bbf\u0b9a\u0bc8\u0baa\u0bcd\u0baa\u0bbe Thiru means \"respect\", visai means \"action\" and pa indicates \"poem\") denotes the ninth volumes of the Tirumurai, the twelve-volume collection of Tamil Saivite devotional poetry.",
    "human_readable": "Thiruvisaippa is a volume that denotes the ninth volumes of the Tirumurai, a twelve-volume collection of Tamil Saivite devotional poetry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9813961386680603,
            "question": "Which volume of the Tirumurai is Thiruvisaippa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9177358746528625,
            "question": "What does Thiruvisaippa denote?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8528189659118652,
            "question": "What is Thiruvisaippa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8043631315231323,
            "question": "Is Thiruvisaippa part of a larger collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721508741378784,
            "question": "How many volumes are in the Tirumurai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6890352964401245,
            "question": "Can you name other volumes within the Tirumurai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5334753394126892,
            "question": "What type of poetry is found in the Tirumurai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5175618529319763,
            "question": "What is the Tirumurai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4696224629878998,
            "question": "To which religious tradition does the Tirumurai belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40581950545310974,
            "question": "What is the religious significance of the Tirumurai?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thiruvisaippa is a volume that denotes the ninth volumes of the Tirumurai, a twelve-volume collection of Tamil Saivite devotional poetry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2306_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which religious tradition does the Tirumurai belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2306_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the Tirumurai?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2306_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of poetry is found in the Tirumurai?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2306_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2306_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the documents, Thiruvisaippa is indeed the ninth volume of the Tirumurai, a twelve-volume collection of Tamil Saivite devotional poetry."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information supporting that Thiruvisaippa (also spelled Thiruvisaipa) is indeed the ninth volume of the Tirumurai, which is described as a twelve-volume collection of Tamil Saivite devotional poetry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}